http://www.precepts.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Contact UsUse the form on the right to contact us.You can edit the text in this area, and change where the contact form on the right submits to, by entering edit mode using the modes on the bottom right.
123 Street Avenue, City Town, 99999
(123) 555-6789
email@address.com
You can set your address, phone number, email and site description in the settings tab.Link to read me page with more information.
About
DONATE
Events
Itinerary
Invite
Free Resources
Articles
Podcast
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyLAST UPDATED: MAY 16, 2018Bob Yandian Ministries ("BYM", “we”, or “us”) is a Christian, nonprofit organization committed to excellence, integrity, and your privacy. This Policy is provided to inform you of the ways BYM collects, uses, stores, transfers and discloses your personal information. By providing your information, you agree to your personal information being processed in accordance with this Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time (as noted in the date above). INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USEBYM collects some anonymous information that cannot be traced back to a specific individual. For example, our web servers automatically record the IP address (the general location where the user is logged) of each visitor to our website, bobyandian.com, and tracks how many people visit the Website. This anonymous information is used to administer and specialize the Website more effectively and gain general information about the backgrounds and sources of visitors. BYM may also ask you to provide personal information that identifies you. we require this information when you visit the Website, submit an inquiry to us, register as a partner, make a purchase or donation, or engage with us for promotional purposes. Such information could include your name, postal address, phone number, email address, or credit card information. BYM limits the personal information it collects to that which is reasonable under the circumstances, and we only collect your personal information with your consent. We use your personal information for the purposes we state or imply when it is collected collection, and we may otherwise use your personal information where permissible by law, for example to respond to an emergency, or in the course of an investigation into illegal behavior. ANTI-SPAMWhere applicable, we will seek your express consent to contact you, including when we contact you via email or other commercial electronic messages. This consent is sought by BYM, and you can contact us as set out below. You can unsubscribe at any time from receiving commercial electronic messages by following the instructions in the message. Even if you have opted out of receiving promotional communications from us, please be aware that we may still contact you for other purposes. For example, we may contact you to provide communications you have consented to receive, regarding the products or services we provide to you, or if you contact us with an inquiry. INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSUREBYM will not rent, sell, lease, or share personal information with other organizations, except in response to subpoenas, court orders, legal processes, or to establish and/or exercise legal rights. Your personal information may be stored, processed or otherwise used by us, our affiliates or our service providers. For example, where you make a purchase on the Website, we may transfer your email address to the shipper for tracking purposes. SAFEGUARDS AND RETENTIONBYM takes all reasonable steps to protect the security and confidentiality of your personal information. We protect the personal information within our custody or control with appropriate organizational, technological and physical safeguards. We store personal information in electronic and physical files that are secure, and our security measures include restricted access to records and data processing equipment, password protocols, and encryption and security software. We only retain personal information for as long as is necessary for the purpose for which it was collected. When we no longer are required to retain the information, we will destroy, erase, or de-identify the information. Legal requirements, however, may require us to retain some or all of the personal information we hold for a period of time that is longer than that for which we might otherwise hold. COOKIESCookies are small data files that can be placed on hard drives by websites visited. The only personal information that a cookie can contain is the information that is provided. BYM uses cookies to gather and store personal information that is collected when online transactions occur through the Website, as well as passwords (used for secure login) and preferences of partners visiting the Website. MINOR POLICYWe do not knowingly collect children’s personal information. Users under the age of 18 must ask parent or guardian permission to use this Website, request information from BYM, or purchase any resources on this Website. THIRD PARTY LINKSThe Website may contain links to other websites operated by third parties. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to the personal information that we collect or receive from third parties with your consent and we cannot be responsible for personal information that third parties may collect, store and use, including through their websites. You should always read the privacy policy of each website you visit carefully. In addition, when you provide to us information on a third party website or platform, the information may also be collected by the third party website and may be subject to their privacy policy. CONTACT BYMBYM strives to keep all personal information complete, up-to-date and accurate. You or a person authorized on your behalf has the right to request to see and obtain a copy of your personal information and to request changes or corrections to inaccurate or incomplete information. If you have any questions or concerns with respect to your personal information or our information practices, please direct your inquiry to: Bob Yandian MinistriesP.O. Box 55236Tulsa, OK 74155918.250.2207bym@bobyandian.com
Contact Us
Salvation Prayer
Facebook
FAQs
Privacy Policy
Subscribe
Terms
© 2019 Bob Yandian Ministries. All Rights Reserved.
